Heat. Heat.
Hey
doo.
H am I audible? Hello everyone.
A warm good morning to all. Hello. Hello
audio ball. Yeah, my audio setup has
been reseted.
So yes, hello Dal. Good morning. A warm
good morning.
So uh today I just wanted to like do a
chat free chat stream where I basically
just yap while I work on some stuff.
Uh I'm a bit sleepd deprived because I
woke up early. I had uh I had
only a few hours of sleep today.
Uh I was supposed to have classes
apparently. Uh there were no classes.
Uh the my sensor couldn't show up. So I
So yeah,
that happened.
So I thought of like taking my time to
like
um get some work done,
study some a little bit and stuff. I got
I could keep doing it on stream so I
could like chat with people who come by
today. So yeah, hence I'm here.
Yes.
Um.
H. Okay. One second.
Okay.
One second. I have to do some stuff
here.
Okay, that should be good enough.
So, yeah. Um,
last stream was day before yesterday.
So, Wednesday was my last stream. Yeah.
Yeah, Wednesday was my last stream.
I honestly wanted to stream yesterday,
but
I was like
uh yesterday too there was no classes,
but
I uh
walked on some stuff for a bit and then
I took a nap and that nap literally
went up to like how many hours again?
Then I went up to
um
3:00 p.m.
Yeah,
that nap went up to 3:00 p.m. and I
thought of doing a stream then I was
like okay I have to do some chores I
have to do some preparations etc
revision thingy and like some uh writing
for this of a thing so I I was like okay
fine
I'm going skip stream let's do it
tomorrow and hence I thought of doing it
in the morning or else I would have um
started my stream around 4 or 5:00 p.m.
Yeah.
Um,
one second
just to tweet that I'm live.
Oh boy.
Okay. Tweet it.
Um,
do this. Do that.
I honestly want to show my screen, but I
felt like Yeah, it's a bit
um
ah Uh
second
um
so many things.
Well, apparently I see on Twitter that
is coming in Fortnite as an icon series
skin. Crazy, you know. Um, if you didn't
know, we were supposed to do a
a Fortnite stream last month, and I
actually um
Yeah, I actually bought the kissing ice
cream
even though I didn't have to. Um,
I bought like a kiss in the eye can and
and uh I haven't even opened or I
haven't ever opened
um Fortnite ever since. I just bought
it. That's it.
I just bought it and that's it.
And also like
also like um
what is it called? Um
uh no. Oh wait, it didn't send out that.
Wait a minute. Cloudfare, what's going
on with you?
Cloud of prayer.
I just realized my stream is not
announced on Discord. Oh,
bro.
What happened?
Arch block. GitHub thumbnail not found.
Okay.
Uh finalized. Oh, that's okay. Where is
the announcement?
Where is the announcement? You're
supposed to make an announcement.
You're supposed to No live streams
found. What?
Engine start. Push to events. Okay. Uh,
I think I need to change this. Wow.
run time.
Hello, Obnoxious Agnostics. It's been a
while. How have you been? Good morning.
How's the weather like in India? Uh,
good question. Let me just look it up. I
don't know. I It was like normal.
Yeah, it's normal for me actually.
Uh, it's normal like 29 Celsius.
29 Celsius. Yeah.
Yep. 29 Celsius.
Oh my god.
Uh it's hard for me to uh know because
uh my whenever I'm in my room, right, my
PC room, stream room, um my room tends
to get super hot.
Probably it's because of the p my
systems uh PC stuff
and my AC literally got tripped. Like I
don't know what happened recently. My AC
got tripped. shipped as in
um there was like a power cut or
electrical malfunction recently
and it literally destroyed the AC is so
that's a bit pain
um
stream engine one secondh
Uh why is it that I have to trigger this
manually
weird
run
YouTube access token acquire? Okay.
Okay. Okay. I thought I had to
authenticate
linking what they call
okay
playlist. Oh,
I have to work on this. And is there
another vegetarian? Is there any meat
you won't eat? I don't know. Actually,
I'm I eat I'm a nonveg person. I do eat
vegetarian food, too. I'm not a picky
eater. No.
So, I eat everything you give me.
Yeah.
Um,
regarding meat,
I eat everything, I guess. Yeah.
Chicken.
Chicken be with
pork. What else?
Duck. Making common duck. Yeah.
Uh, what else?
Yeah. also. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. Also me. Yum. Yum. Uh, when it
comes to vegetable vegetables, uh,
is there anything I don't like?
H
when it comes to vegetables,
I think,
okay, I like tomatoes. Yeah, I started
to like tomatoes over the years. Yeah.
Then broccoli is actually good. I ate
broccoli for the first time when I had
ramen
uh ramen noodles. When I had it, they
had like broccoli. I was like, "Wow,
this is nice. I like the taste of this."
Like a pure uh like
vegetables, right? Healthy for your
body.
And
I don't think I don't have anything.
Yeah, if there's any vegetables I never
had before, uh
probably it will take some time for me
to get used to it.
What mra do you decide when you're
meditating? I don't meditate much
actually.
Um
I don't meditate much.
I think I need to do that. No. Yeah.
Meditation is good for your health and
mindset.
I would love to do some meditation in
these days because I'm like super
stressed these days
like a lot of things on my mind
overwhelmed
anxious exams are there
I'm moving
so many things so I'm like h
that's also one of the reasons why I was
like hesitant to stream
cuz like uh I have like so much
priorities in my head uh I have to give
attention to. So I don't think I can
have.
Have you tried dura ma? What is that?
No, I haven't.
What is this?
No, I have not tried this.
Wait, why is my Google search in Hindi?
I can't read Hindi. Or is there no
uh I can't read. What? How do I make it
English?
What? What is this?
Google.com.
Wait, why is it Wait, is
Okay. Okay, it's working.
Don't mind me if I'm being a little bit
of silent. I'm just a bit
uh what do you call it? Uh
lack of sleep. So, I'm a bit tired, I
guess.
I thought of just uh talking. Yeah.
Yeah. chatting with you all and like um
just get some work stuff work done and
go to sleep by 10 or 12
I think. No way I have a I will have a
important call. I have to attend like
Oh god. Yeah, I had to give my details
and everything.
Yeah, bank stuff, Forex or whatever.
Uh cuz I had to pay my fees now for my
tuition and everything from next month.
I had to pay it in JPY.
So yeah. Uh hello M. Hello. Hello.
Long time. Yes. Long time. Hello. How
are you?
Happy belated holy.
Happy belated holy m. How is life?
How have been streams and everything?
I've been so out of loop.
I've been watching no one. I've been I'm
barely on YouTube.
Paperwork suck. Yes, true. True. It
sucks.
It really sucks.
Uh
Have you been streaming Hollow Night?
Nice
games. I haven't been touching uh games
at all. I I I used to be active in Blue
Protocol doing just the dailies and now
I stopped doing that too.
Stuck in a backlog of videos. H. Oh,
you're editing and stuff.
You're editing and stuff. Nice.
Uh,
Google Fiber Wi-Fi 7 router. What is
this video? I just got recommended. What
the heck?
G Fiber.
Wow.
As a fiber. What?
Damn. Nice.
Interesting.
Oh, 12 gigs of video. Oh, you're
editing. Oh my god. It And it's only too
long. Oh, crazy.
Oh, you must have put your bit rate
high. Oh, it's like Oh, damn.
Damn nice.
Uh,
speaking of videos, which Oh my god, I
also have 8,000 bit. Oh, then how come?
Wait, if you have like a 40 series GPU
plus
40 40 series, 50 series, do it in AV1
maybe. So lower uh lesser the
lesser the bit rate higher the quality
kind of thingy.
8,000 with three you get 4K quality.
Uh because of Twitch proxy files. Oh. Oh
wait. You Oh wait Twitch streams. No
wait. You could export them right
or you could YouTube DLP that. Right.
Oh, wait. Uh, YouTube DLB or Twitch
downloader CLI. Uh, GUI is there if you
prefer GUI or CLI is there. My GitHub
action which I recently made uh is doing
the CLI stuff for Twitch to fetch the
uh to fetch the VA ID and the chat and
everything.
I recently did that
and I link it to my YouTube ID. So
I record while Okay. Okay.
All that stuff
you know YouTube compression is so bad.
Speaking of recording and uh uploading
stuff now video stuff I have to like
upload so many backlogs of video uh
streams to Billy Billy and when I since
I download YouTube VOD right video a
live stream VOD it's just sad how blurry
and messy the quality is hello bacon
good morning
how is mat
I I saw you were playing marathon baked
good. How are you?
I I I start to stream again. I'm back to
streaming. He
amazing dog. Why? You're making me want
to buy it.
The thing is I'm super broke. I have to
buy essential stuff for packing my
luggage, everything. I I can't spare
money. And out of nowhere, my Twitter
feed is saying like,
uh, Hol Life Suicide is coming to
Fortnite. I want to get her skin in
Fortnite. I'm like, bro, I broke. I am
broke.
Take care of the prep first. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's like I can always get
marathon later.
Yeah.
It it sucks that I um only
play I could only play marathon only
like 30 minutes when the server slam was
up
and that's about it. And I did the
tutorial I was like oh my god damn. And
I matched for I played one match and I
died instantly to a robot or something
and it tried to uh feed on my health or
life. It pulled out its weird uh creepy
uh wires and started to suck out my life
uh energy or something.
Um
it's crazy.
Yeah, really surprising how my PC was
able to uh play that game
and like marathon thingy was um
it's fully the aesthetics and
everything. No, more environment
and less stuff. I guess people or Yeah,
bots are there. But still, I'm like too
attracted to the environment and the
area and the design and stuff and and
it's crazy.
Time to buy Scissor 7. Scissor 7. Isn't
that that cartoonish kind of or
cartoonish? Sorry. Animeish thingy with
this guy.
Ah, yeah. Yeah, this one. Okay. Okay.
Wait. Is this a cartoon or anime? Wait.
I don't think it's Wait.
Is it an anime?
Okay. It's Dongwa. Okay. Sorry. Sorry. I
called it Kato. I'm sorry. It's a
Dongwa.
Uh,
it's way lighter than Arc for sure.
Crazy is a game writer exploration.
Hey, Dongha. Dong Hua.
Man is Chinese manas like um uh comics
uh colored comics. Then Dong Hua
is like anime. Yeah, Chinese anime.
animator series.
It's way lighter than Arc.
You saw that loading screen. It's
literally a moth eating something and
I'm like, "What the heck?
What the heck?" Weird, but also cool.
Yeah, it's on sale. It's on the It's in
the front page of Steam, I believe. If
you go to store, uh the first thing you
see is marathon now available
and it's like 2,500,
not 2,450.
2,450.
Yeah,
it was free for three week uh 3 days. uh
like a like a trial thingy you can say.
Um
yeah, the art direction is nice. It's
like inspirational if you're an u
designer artist and stuff, right? If
you're into this uh media stuff. Oh,
yeah. We can you're studying art and
media stuff, right?
So, yeah, it's like inspirational.
Yeah.
the art direction everything like
it'll be analyzing it and like
understanding why did the artist
lead artist um art directive why did
they chose this how it affect the colors
etc
everything like crazy
uh
and I have to say for another two years
oh my god [\h__\h]
Damn.
Yeah, I'm broke as well, man.
The thing I uh
kind of felt sad is
I bought Arc Raiders
and I'm not even playing it much.
Is it because of the PC or is it because
I I don't think I got burned out of it?
I I think it's mainly the fact that I
can't stream it and play it.
Uh and the times I streamed all
five, six, seven streams, I every time I
stream I have bad luck and I died. I
lost to good loot. But when I uh play
the game off stream, I I win. I extract
easily. I get good loot.
It It's weird.
So, uh
it will be weird.
Streamers.
Yeah,
that could be true. Yes.
Oh, I did not update the image. What?
Man, recently I've been moving
everything to the cloud. All of my Sammy
stuff which runs locally on my PC. I'm
moving everything to GitHub and
Cloudfare.
Everything is automated. Discord
notification announcement event
website archive page chat transcript AI
generated summary everything is
automated now.
But everything is breaking. I don't get
it.
How are you doing? I'm doing mixed
emotions. I guess I'm stressed man.
There's so many things in my brain right
now like exam stuff 15 next Sunday like
15th exam.
Uh I'm I'm falling behind in Japanese
stuff. Uh kanji and everything.
Uh then what preparation since I'm
leaving
and uh registering gang? Yeah. And then
I have to clean up my PC as in format my
PC by next week like Monday or or before
Friday ASAP or at least before 20th.
I haven't backed up anything to the
cloud. I have to back up so many things.
How to delete so many unwanted things.
All the best though. Thank you.
I'm confused about the laptop.
I actually was too into this. Uh so
there was this viewer who uh like long
back I mean long not long back like uh
last last month January or something. I
I forgot. He was like, "Uh, you should
get like uh Asus Rock Sticks
G16 2025 edition." Ever since he told me
that, I looked at it, looked it up, and
it's like really good laptop. I've been
so obsessed with it. Then I realized
then I realized,
yeah, it's expensive. Why do I need to
spend that much money on that on a
laptop which where I could use that much
money to build a PC, right? That's like
it's two lakh
two lakh 2.5 lakh, right? Why do I need
to buy that much? Of course, buying it
from Japan, it will be a little bit
cheaper, but still that's too much now.
So, I've been thinking of getting
something uh cheaper
like at least a 40 series laptop cuz AV1
I could use AV1 in OBS,
right?
And
yeah,
50 series is just better. But I can
always build a laptop after saving up.
I'll be doing part-time and everything.
So yeah, I'll buy gear slowly, so it's
fine.
Ah,
boy. Yes.
God, I I hope I can stream.
It's going to be hard, but yeah, I'll do
my best next month on which got to be
focused. Not
nowadays. I see myself always chat GPT
whether it be studies or stream related
stuff I just talk to it and be like yeah
you know
talk to me I don't have much people to
talk to yeah most of the time it's
probably uh mainly I
uh ask GPT for like
my ideas in my brain right like all
these stream stuff.
Yeah,
it's weird how I'm addicted to this.
Wait, are you guys addicted to like prom
AI prompting or like talking to AI
about stuff?
I'm addicted to it. I don't know why.
It's weird.
The recent thing I talked with was um
like 30 minutes ago. Wait, when when did
I start with my stream? 35, right? It's
35 minutes, right? Yeah. Yeah. So, 40
minutes ago, I was asking how can I
how can I link
when I schedule a stream on YouTube, how
can I link that schedule stream on
Twitch schedules? like if I'm where to
use the Twitch Helix API, what endpoint
should I use and how can I do it in
Cloudfare worker so I can do it
automatically on a Chrome timer and I'll
use my own uh o to a stuff and uh guide
me how can I do this and stuff and I I
asked that and he gave me the thing. I
was like, "Okay,
I'm going to do it while I stream."
Maybe
I use it as an unpaid intern who does
all the searching for products. Um, and
Chi video is free, right? Uh, for India
for like 18 months or 16 months or
something, right? Yeah. I I think my
plan ends by 2026
of November. Yeah, I got it on November.
Oh,
damn. They have to pay.
I don't want to
You shouldn't
add it too much. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The
thing is that I don't know coding now.
That's why that's why that's why I'm
like every time asking like how do I do
this? How do I make my website better?
How to do this? How to do that? This and
that.
Half of this stuff it's literally stream
related. Even though I'm not streaming,
it's pro mostly behind the scenes
streaming related architecture
infrastructure stuff. Crazy.
Wow.
Yeah.
Man, this hot water is so tasty. I don't
know why I needed this.
But yeah, it's so weird. I don't know
why I'm into this. I'm a nerd. Why do I
nerd into this tech related stuff even
though I'm not a coder or anything?
But uh
like I have one idea then I expand that
idea and it becomes bigger bigger bigger
and it becomes like a big
detour.
Crazy.
Hello
Don't depend emotionally on it. On that
it's danger. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I don't I
don't
Yeah, I don't do that. Oh, I only do it
for uh work.
Yeah, stream stuff. That's it.
You know me, V. I I don't like to do too
many button presses.
Uh, so I'm like, yeah, how can I
automate it?
One click does everything. I stream and
stream automatically does everything for
me kind of thingy.
Wait. Uh,
wait. How do I say
Yeah, I'm so tired today cuz I couldn't
sleep much. I was like
studying and doing homework which I was
supposed to do
yesterday and day before yesterday when
I was sick
and I I slept at
10.
Yeah, I slept off on the desk while
doing homework
and I woke up at 12 and then I slept
again. I woke up at 2:00. Then I was
from two 2 to 3. Yeah, 3:00 a.m. was
this own like uh what do you call it? Uh
I I had this weird idea like how do I
link
uh I I was just pitting at 3:00 a.m. in
the morning today. I was like
I was like um
how can I
move my
uh chat logs I have on my discord on to
like uh my website or something on a
something or maybe to cloudfare
etc. I was talking to it and then it
tell me told me about the privacy thingy
and everything. It's not good to like
keep like an public database for user
chats.
Even if a user on YouTube or Twitch or K
are chatting online, most of the
platform itself uh they only gave gave
the moderators and or broadcasters to
read the user chat history now. So it's
not good to Yeah. Yeah. All those stuff.
Yeah. Then I
was studying revising grammar. How long
it take you to learn Japanese? Uh
coursewise
no. Yeah. Uh coursewise uh I started
learning an year ago, December of last
year.
Uh
yeah, I I knew Japanese here and there
because of anime
and I used to watch
Japanese media. No
like Japanese
like Twitch
live streams etc. I used to watch. So I
could understand a bit
and because of that I I I could I was
able to
do well in N5 but since I did not
practice I lost touch and I'm bad at
reading
everything right now and struggling in
N4 level.
Uh I had a break
uh digital footprints. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Yes. And that's one thing too.
I'm trying to I think I can show um
uh jok.space
live streams archive.
Okay. Uh
so this was
Oh, this is two days. Uh this is yeah
last stream right I'm trying to
so here you have YouTube chat right all
the people who came by on YouTube you're
here
I want to put Twitch chat here that's
the thing I got the streams Twitch chat
it's here GitHub
I got the Twitch chat
uh that archive wave
and jockn
uh normalized, right? So, this is all
the people uh like all the chats from
Twitch on last stream. I just have to
merge it
and make it readable on site from the
archive page. Why is the thumbnail
broken?
O
to fix that.
Don't worry, John. academically. I want
to give up. I'm so d Oh my god.
And I need to change the AI summary
thingy. This is bad.
This is a bit weird,
you know. Um
Yeah, I was looking uh like if you go to
any video and uh summarize it. No, like
last stream.
Pause it. If you ask AI and summarize
it, it gives you a good thing like all
the key points and everything. No, I
want this kind of thingy.
I think I need to change my prompt.
Yeah, I think I need to change my
prompt. So, the chapters is made by the
AI. than this thingy. I think I have to
ask for key points maybe.
Did you know uh Google Gemini how it
summarizes is based on your transcript
and the Yeah, it reads your transcript,
not the video. Listen, uh reads your
transcript of the video and then
summarizes it. Then it gives you the
timestamps
for this. Really nice. Oh,
I'm like I could replicate this but if I
switch to Gemini but I have to pay now
to use Gemini
Tox. I use this thing Gro Q.
I use this
Grock not the
G gritter
X Grock. Yeah, this has a free uh free
plan.
This has a free plan. I think I'm using
the llama version. Yeah. Yeah. A llama
meta AI, I think. I'm not sure.
Really nice.
I initially thought it was Gro Gro. Then
I was like, okay, that's something else
with a similar name. Nice.
Uh,
okay. I'm
going to try debugging this.
Ah, so many things.
But yeah, you can like uh check if you
wish to look at the archives.
Um, let me put the archive page.
I have to design the CSS.
working progress
page.
There you go.
Yeah, I've designed the ar the archives
page, but archive pages, dynamic pages.
Yeah.
O
Gro and Gro. Oh, wait. Wait. It's G.
Wait. It's not G R O K.
Oh, wait. It is. Wait. What is G O R K?
Gorok is a popular edgy parodi AI
account on X with 85K followers. What?
What?
X Gro. Yeah. Okay. Yes.
Wow.
Nice.
Uh Ta.
Time to get coffee, I guess. Yes. Have a
coffee break.
Take a rest.
Yeah.
So,
uh, what do I have to do today? Yes, I
have to fix my
storage.
Let me do it. Rest out for the weak
links.
Oh my god.
stream up. Okay, I have to delete some
stuff, right?
Edit.
I'm a week as in week of the month. So,
I'm a residence call in star or YT. H
mean
control shift M.
Oh boy. So much of that uh
I was only supposed to log recent
streams.
I ended up pressing
a wrong button like come at this thing
and it ended up logging like last 50
streams
to the database and I'm like oh my god
why.
Hello, Francoa.
It's been a while. Hello. Hello.
How are you? Good morning.
A warm good morning to you.
I just said, "No, you're not." And
crush. Oh my god.
Yeah. Bye.
Good morning, Franco. How you how you
doing this fine day?
I have to check uh all
bits.
Where is that long hash?
Long B 64. Oh my. Okay, got it. Uh, of
C4. Okay. OFC for
Oh, this is my waiting room. Ah, I still
had this scheduled on YouTube. Oh my
god, that's
Oh, wait. Why is private unlisted
streams getting logged? What? Okay,
I have to fix that.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't save. Don't save.
Don't save. Okay.
Why did you change from Why did YouTube
change from showing username to showing
ads? Oh, I think it's like a new thing.
Uh cuz they introduced username thingy
uh for uh when they introduced username
thingy, they made it priority for
comments, right? Then they changed it uh
made that stuff be affected for uh live
streams as well over the time.
But there is an extension
for browsers
where it instead of showing the
username, it'll show your display name.
I forgot the name of the extension.
But there is an extension which does
that. You can if you want you can do
that too.
Uh
and uh there's like this comment
commenting platform
just like streamer bot all those stuff
like stream tools right this is what
what uh this is what JPvtubers use
called one com someone made like a
onecom extension so it shows you the
display name of the user rather than the
user her name.
Yeah, I saw it on Twitter. I think I
bookmarked it or something. It's been so
long.
Uh, it's pretty nice.
Oh my god, another one. I found another
one. Okay. Uh,
who is this guy? Uh,
oh, this was my last stream. Okay. Okay.
XB T A RB.
Okay. I need to find
uh this got event. Okay, event image.
Oh, image. Okay, I need to remove this.
You know, I accidentally made a mistake.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I I know that. Uh so,
there's two ways you can do it. There is
an extension. Uh if you are streaming on
Twitch, you can have that. Uh no, three
ways. Uh on Twitch, there's an extension
uh like a channel extension called
Oh, wait. What was the extension name?
Just search for uh Dan Maki chat. That's
on Twitch as an overlay extension.
Second one is on stream elements.
There is a Dan Maku chat. If you're into
stream elements, there's a Dan Maku
bullet chat extension.
I just it's in a GitHub I believe. Then
recently
our local uh stream profi
made an uh members only extension.
So you have to use his uh extension, the
chat uh multi chat extension which
supports YouTube kick, Twitch. It's for
members only. So you have to pay the $10
members thingy and you can download it
and use it forever kind of thingy.
Yeah, Nati made one recently. You didn't
see the video he made on on Wait, did he
upload? I think he made a YouTube short.
Yeah,
he made a YouTube shot about it.
And I was there when he was uh decoding
the I was watching his stream and he was
coding the Danma code thingy. He was
thinking he was like asking his chat
what name should he uh name what name
should he use for this extension. I was
like, "Is that the Danmaku bullet chart
you see on Nikon Nikotv and Billy
Billy?"
And he was like, "Yes, finally someone
knows what this is."
So he went with the Daku thingy bullet
chat for his extension name.
I didn't watch Ni stream stuff.
Really cool.
Man, I wish I I wish to use streamer
board. Only if I knew coding, I could
have
done. But yeah, here's Dharmaku chat
allows you to have like a layer thingy.
So the chats can float in your face and
behind you and in between you.
So if you're a YouTuber
uh your mo it will show in front of your
model and behind your model and behind
your assets like table or whatever
background you have like in front for
foreground elements right it will show
that too
really good
the one offline four months I was
offline Man,
most of the time just old videos so I
avoid it.
Man, I s I I was seeing um so many since
since the new Elgato
next thingy, right? Everyone is like
attacking voice meter. Everyone is like
voice meter is dead. Go for Elgato
Wavelength 3.
And I saw the voice m Twitter was like
saying to people like yeah voice meter
and Elgato are different products.
We provide more stuff right
but yeah the use case of voice meter is
really advanced not for your average
streamer.
It's for like audio engineers and
everything. Hey can anyone can use it.
That's there too. It's a bit complicated
now, but Elgato made it more simpler
with their routing table thingy.
It's just pain to set a wave. You know,
my configuration
disappeared when I updated to the stable
version. I was on beta for beta 4, I
guess. Wait, what's the current version?
Oh, beta 3 uh 3.0. Oh, no. Right. When
this version beta came out, I was on the
beta version of this current stable
version. And when they released the
stable, they had like a new driver or
something. They're all like their old
driver link. You can manually drive
download a driver. That did not work for
me. Apparently, my Windows settings
was the install default apps
was on a different local drive rather
than C drive. That's why uh you can't I
couldn't install the driver of
the wavelength driver. I re Yeah, I
restart uninstalled and reinstalled and
I lost my configuration. I am like bro.
I set up so much EQ and everything.
I set up so many things. I put every
single game,
etc. And
rip.
I have to make sure I'm for my acoustic
so I can't get my
but yeah they should add a way for you
to um
they should add a way for you to
um back up your stuff.
Honestly,
it is just hard and sad like you can't
like back up
your or cloud save your data. No,
speaking of which, uh I I don't know if
I can take my stream deck pedal
and I don't want to keep it here. I want
to take it with me even though I won't
use it. It's Elgato product. It's a
premium product. I don't want to keep it
dusted up somewhere in a corner, you
know.
I I bought this uh stream deck pedal. I
I import Yeah, I got it imported. Had to
pay the customs, etc. It was such a heck
hectic process. I only bought it so I
can use it for collabs and everything
like uh push to talk now for discord
etc. While I'm streaming I can talk to
chat to chat and and and like yeah and
press down on the foot pedal.
Yeah, it's a bit heavyish.
I can't I have a like a weight limit for
the flight. So,
I'm like, uh,
plus I'm taking my mic, one mic. I can't
take my HyperX, so I'll take my fine
mic.
Uh, so yeah,
probably in the future I'll get someone
to like ship it to me or maybe
something. I don't know.
I I can only take limited items with me.
So
like weight wise. Yeah, sadly. Yeah,
that's one thing.
Either way, I don't need much stuff,
right?
So many things.
Oh yeah. Shipping. No. No. I can ask
someone who's coming to Japan.
My teachers or something. They will come
to Japan. No. They come from they go
like come from Japan to India. India to
Japan. I could ask teacher or like one
of the staff members like I can ask my
dad to like pack it up and give it to
them if they're coming then I can go to
them and collect it now if it's really
necessary
right
that yeah
but it's not that much priority so it's
fine
What was the shrimp's ID?
Oh, I need to keep it noted down. Oh,
what?
X X XB PTB. Okay. XB PTB X D X Oh my
god. What did I just say? X. Okay, I got
it.
Okay. PTV, YouTube, uh, what it call
where is Twitch, Twitch, Twitch, Twitch.
Oh, no, no, no. Yes, last stream I
accidentally went live on a wrong
stream. Okay, wait. Where is the
Fortnite stream?
Uh, studio.
Was it C8 BA?
Okay.
I I don't know if I should keep it. on
just chatting and yap about stuff
everyone confused about. Oh [\h__\h] I just
Wait, I think I have a window thingy,
right? Where is that? What happened to
that? Wait, I had like a
thing.
Wait, where is that small little thing I
used to have? Wait.
Uh
oh, yeah, I have this. Oh yeah, I can.
Wait. Uh, let me do this.
Uh,
oh yeah, this one.
Shareable link. Okay. CCV1 FZ.
Okay. I think I can like show this. It's
fine.
Just working thingy.
Make it small so no one notices. It's
fine.
Hi. I have to manually edit this.
So, my GitHub action accidentally
I it's Yeah, this is the Twitch
broadcast. Oh, yeah. You don't see it.
Oh, I'm I'm dumb. Okay, wait.
There you go. I forgot I have a
display capture version of this.
Uh yeah, my Twitch broadcast
what ID is.
So how it links Twitch is actually it
scans no it takes the time stamp of the
Twitch V and compares to the YouTube
stream schedule start time uh yeah time
stamp of the schedule start time and if
it's between that time and 1 hourish
then
yeah it will be linked
cuz uh when I multiream
YouTube always goes first. Then after 5
seconds, Twitch kick, everything boots
up, right? Cuz I'm on multimill, right?
So
yeah, I needed like a fallback system
where if a a stream happened on YouTube
and Twitch stream also uh is on a
similar window within 30 minutes 30 to 1
hour window frame then ling it kind of
thingy
show it actually worked. I have to
remove this from here. This is supposed
to go
somewhere else.
Wait, wait, I can't just I can just link
it like this. Why work? Wait, never
mind.
Okay, horizontal. This is the YouTube
data.
I have everything. monetization
if the every setting enable auto style
privacy
even the HTML embed thingy as well
every single data from YouTube
live thumbnail.
So, I plan to link kick and Twitch to
this system.
So, it's easier now.
This was easier. A bit easier.
And also the playlist is here.
Too much technical diodes are connect.
Okay, this is Oh, it's not JSON valid.
Okay, where did I make Where did I make
a mistake?
No.
Oh, no. Wait, what did I do?
Okay, we don't need this.
And who is this
YouTube?
What?
Uh.
Oh, it's supposed to be like Okay, got
it. Okay, it's working. So, file, no,
edit,
blank operations,
trim both, and eol space.
Okay, copy this and go to CloudFare and
dump it here.
Paste it.
Too much.
Hi, it is done.
Now I go to Oh yeah, this is what I did.
Look at all of the I don't know if you
can see this ma.
This is this is an image. Okay,
this was a Discord image in B 64. I
accidentally
uh I was supposed to set send hash.
I was supposed to send hash image hash
but I accidentally sent the whole
3 MB file that B64
it was for um it was for uh this Discord
event. Uh yeah it was for this this
image
the whole thing.
But I fixed it. I probably fixed it. I
fixed it. Yeah.
um
slash API/
what?
Yeah. By
none.
What the
was
waiting.
It was long. Yes.
So,
did I break it? Oh my. Wait, wait, wait,
wait. What the what the scan,
bro? I broke it. Oh no. Oh no. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I broke
it. I think I broke it. I think I broke
it. Oh no.
Oh no. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Edit.
This
space.
Oh, no. That has that has space. That's
too much space.
Uh, edit
shelling space. Oh, no. That's not the
one. Oh, uh, edit.
It's supposed to be this N.
Then why is it
struggling?
Ah, browser
Tajino browser crashed.
It's broken. So yeah, I have my playlist
YouTube playlist. All my playlist see
our creators is here. Schedule hash is
actually my this thing.
This has a image hash that gets write
written in KV.
Uh, okay. My browser is not responding.
Wow.
H responded
JSON formatter and paste this here.
process it.
Uh
oh, it is correct. Okay. Okay. Then
compat.
Okay. Hopey that
go for elite based ser.
Hi. Uh
API scan. Okay, it works. Yay.
It's working.
Yay!
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, let me go to my GitHub and do this
YouTube
actions.
Oh, it just ran right now. 9:15 a.m. AI.
Okay, what did it generate?
Which video? Which video? Which video?
All videos already processed. Oh, never
mind.
So, it only processes
10 videos at a time. No, not at uh uh
one run is equal to one video. So, it
only can maximum process up to 10, I
believe. Yeah, I I don't process the old
streams only the recent ones. So more I
stream the more AI metadata will be
there.
So the
Okay, it's think I'm in the wrong
repository.
Okay, let's see if it works. Okay.
Uh, Twitch archive.
Want to see it together.
Okay, let's watch it together. Okay,
run.
It's going to download the chat from my
last Twitch stream.
That's Twitch downloaded CLI
cookies. Okay, bye.
Uh, fetching wallet skipping chat.
Yeah, this is today's stream.
Wait, is this today, right? Oh, wait.
This is the live stream stream, right?
So,
twitch.tv
twitch t twitch.tv/
video/
is that how you do it?
No, no, it's not. Okay, that's not how
you do it. M, how do you how do you
access a video?
Uh, what's the URL for a video?
Uh,
okay. Videos. Okay, got it. Yeah. Yeah,
it's the same ID. See, see, it's the
same ID. So, this first live stream will
always be skipped. It's always the
second one, V one, which will be
returned.
Yeah.
And uh apparently my linker is in
cloudfare.
I may just do that.
Uh platform linger
blood linger.
I have to fix this, right?
Wait, why am I showing this? Wait,
I shouldn't publicly show this.
I mean, no, I can't I do much cuz I have
security on this. So, it's fine.
Okay. Link slash
Twitch. Okay.
L / Twitch
Lord Mendry
Checking V.
Gorilla def check. Def check. Skipping
private video. Diff check. Diff check.
Def check.
Time title match. Match found 27134
is equal to XPTt. Linking complete. Wow.
Wait. So that's the
uh Twitch TV slash video slash.
Okay.
Okay. That was yesterday's stream. Yes,
I finally linked it. Let's go.
Oh my god. Nice. Okay. Nice. Nice. Nice.
Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice.
Nice.
And now what?
Now uh
okay now we process this right um
uh
stream engine yeah stream engine
code
uh
okay wait format this okay okay
I need your I'll pick.
Okay. Uh platform linking worker. Okay.
This one.
Ah what did I have to do here again?
So Twitch archive comes from GitHub.
Then platform linking worker happens and
links to stream map stream and then
archive worker happens.
Hey, wait. What the wait? What do I
need? An archiver.
Um,
remove incorrect link from previous. Oh
yeah, I have to do this cuz I
accidentally linked the wrong stream,
right? So it has like passes it has to
do. So it's like one the 30 minute to 1
hour window for a video. Second is the
title ma matching title. Twitch, YouTube
title has to be similar or some somewhat
similar
80% of the time. In case if I change my
Twitch title to be something different,
no, but the same title format
uh I use reject, right? So reject wise
it can fetch the thingy and like m uh
make it matched.
Then what was third one was
yeah mele two is enough I guess two
methods for the linking
that's what I did if I remember
what The
archive API
uh
m uh oh yeah archive API yeah website I
forgot you you are the one who's
responsible for this yesa
Uh
pass chat. Okay.
So I dumb the whole code
here.
Cloudf fair.
Oh, wait. Where is the Oh, no.
M. What the
hell?
detect
when a new stream is detected.
Wait, what is this? Ah, this was the
thing I said like I was said uh asking
GPT at 3:00 a.m. like how do I do the
automated
Twitch schedule linking from YouTube?
Ah, that one.
That's not the one. Where is it?
From linking. No.
No. No. [\h__\h] No.
Oh,
worker architecture.
I forgot.
Okay. So, this is my
next archive
API worker
and
So I currently wish to
link my Twitch chat
which is in uh GitHub repo which is
automated using
GitHub actions.
Uh
let me get the link.
which data archive is
so
basically the normalized. Yeah,
this is the normalized version of the
Twitch of the Twitch chat. I wish
make this available available on my
website
for the archive page
to check the code here.
Oh,
uh, I already
uh did the YouTube
YouTube. Uh,
bro, when you have too many things,
you forget where things are.
you forget where things are honestly um
YouTube stuff along with the
with the subtitles etc. So to check this
for code and
tell me how I
can in the create the link
uh the
chat link
here.
I will also have big chat
too in the future.
Okay,
copy this.
You know, it was kind of hard when I was
like not on PC. I was on my phone on um
like Android Google uh Chrome app using
desktop mode trying to do this
everything on your phone. It was hard
cuz my P like my room was so hot without
the AC and I'm like bro I don't want to
go up to my PC. It's too hot. I will be
literally a boiling egg. I'll get
migraine and headache. I don't want to
go up. I was like yeah
I think that's one of the reasons why I
fel feel so tired too.
Yeah.
And even now I'm like having headaches.
O
multi-reo support
change this router. Okay. Change the
router.
Put this here.
Find the thingy.
And uh
now the API becomes archive video ID
chat/
YouTube. Archive video ID chat/apchat/
Twitch. Oh, I can do that.
Oh, nice.
F action const part
five H
rewrite your entire handle chat
handler with this.
GitHub fet
live chat video ID video ID. Okay.
Okay.
Chat normalized. Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Replace your entire Okay.
Global handlers
overlay
transcript handle chat.
Oh yeah, this is the one right. Oh yeah.
is dizz
update handle info
inside. Okay.
Handle full H.
Handleful.
F U L.
H I
handle.
Replace the chat section. Okay.
Handleful. Oh, this guy
con.
Is it that really? Okay. Wait.
Okay, there's an error. H
Con's YT chat address uh fetch in
GitHub. Okay. Con's YouTube chat. Uh
JSON Twitch chat Twitter address. Okay.
A very catch.
Uh then what?
Then change to return.
Okay. Return is there something return.
Okay. Where is return?
Uh
change to red dawn.
Chunk
Veron though.
Oh, wait. I'm so confused. What the
heck? Wait,
catch
and modify meta
const hash
chat. Ah, this guy.
Wait, no.
What
length?
Ah, this guy. Okay. Okay. Okay. Got it.
Got it. Got it. Got it.
Chat length. Okay.
M
uh for largest side this will be slow
much better architecture will be KV no
so your front end can do
API/archchive video ID chat/ twitch or
API render everything oh I rendered the
full okay okay nice that's good
oh that is
Also, what betray my streaming?
One second.
Wait, how do I see my picture?
Oh, Twitch enhanced broadcasting.
Interesting.
Oh, wait. I did I don't I have to make
like a Okay.
Okay. Wait. Um
one second. Um
working in background.
Okay, there you go.
So people who drop by won't be like
confused. What is who why is he speaking
yapping like this? Well, what is he
talking about?
Okay. So,
and also I just have to mention
so in stream
map
the directory
will be
stream
video ID dot
dot twitch dot
Oh, I actually forgot. Um,
switch.
No, wait. It's something called vaude,
right?
Oh my god, I can't search.
Uh,
I remember the
body URL. So, I'll just copy that.
Nashio.
Yeah, I can 100% confirm my PC dies when
I load this database.
My busy dies and that is not good.
What the heck?
Gorilla back from the void. Okay, I'll
just search this
YouTube vertical horizontal
Discord
Twitch. Okay, got it. Vaude ID.
Twitch dot broadcast dot.
You know what? We'll just
quit all the metall
stuff.
Also
kind of confused
confused
on the handle full stuff. It did replace
replace
that.
Where do I post?
Sending love from beam family. Hello
Bergie 75126. Hello. Hello. Welcome.
Hope you're doing well. Hello. Hello.
Uh where do I put uh where do I
put the return and
my stuff?
Uh
I already have. Okay.
Find the section right below it.
Right. Okay. Wait. Find the section.
Hope you're having a great stream. Yes,
I'm having a great show. I'm just
working behind
uh beh in the background
and yapping.
Yeah.
Okay. This one. And what else do I need
here too?
Right below it.
Okay.
Uh, okay. I need to copy this.
I bet there's two of them. Uh
oh. Handleful. Okay, got it. this guy,
right? Paste this
stream data.
uh
immediately below this.
Okay.
Cons charas.
Consus
chas.
Oh yeah. Got it.
Remove it. Put it like this.
All right.
And replace it with modify metadata.
Find the section and
has
where is it? I can't find it.
playlist.
As has as as
as chat. Oh, got it.
Okay, now what? Uh, scroll to the bottom
of
Yeah. items dot. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
need to change the items.
to
chat. YouTube chat. Okay, got it.
Nice.
Inside handle overview.
Your final API looks like this. Okay.
Right now worker fetches two GitHub
repos. Better design
repo one two. Okay. If Twar gets larger
then you should store it in RV
R2 KV. No, I don't want no
Okay. What all stuff did I do right now?
Oh my god, I'm so confused. Oh,
YouTube chat.
Oh, wait. I think I have a duplicated
version of this. Oh, no.
the async function, right?
Oh, yeah. This guys, these guys. Oh, no.
After the transcribe
M.
Okay, let's screenshot this.
So, I accidentally duplicated it. Hey, I
did. Oh, wait. What?
I did. I'm so dumb.
Oh, I did duplicate it. Oh, I'm so dumb.
Dumb.
Okay, fix the code. Let's go. Copy this.
Okay, fix that.
Do check the four cord.
Okay, finally.
F platform Twitch.
Okay.
I would love to check this. Oh god. Oh.
Okay. Wait. Um, if platform is equal to
Twitch
to this
format.
Uh, okay.
H
Oh, it's 10. It's already 10 a.m. Oh my
god.
Okay, I think I'm done.
Okay, deploy. Let's see if it works.
Okay, how do I check this? Um, I forgot.
I forgot. I forgot. Um,
right now your worker does eight
sequential fetches. Fetch, transcribe,
index, fetch, stream, summary, chapters,
transcribe, YouTube chat, Twitch chat,
playlist, fetch waits for the previous
one.
Clify workers can run them in parallel.
What example
promis
latency will grow. Oh boy.
That could be bad for us, doesn't it?
Once I add kick chat to the archiver
then I can think about it, I guess.
Yeah.
So done me.
Drink more water.
All right.
Live stream archive.
That's one.
So, the condent is okay. It's broken.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
I have to fix you.
archive.
API dot
dot da dot.
It's not here. chat dot Okay, it's here.
YouTube dot Okay, YouTube chat.
Ah, good. Wonderful. Oh my god, look at
this. A nice. Okay, wait. I can show you
guys this.
All right. So, this is a YouTube
channel. Okay. I'm going to
duplicate this.
It's a bit slow cuz too much data it has
to load. Right. Rename this as
uh Twitch chat.
Go here. Collopsible.
Collopsible content.
Yeah, I have to rename this
uh Twitch chat.
Okay. So, go to data available here. I
just change the last line to dot
Twitch.
Haha.
What?
Wait, does it have more? Wait, why is it
zero? Wait. Oh, yeah. Yeah, this does
not have TW. Oh, yeah. My bad. Sorry.
Uh,
I I can fix this. Uh, this should be
YouTube chat.
Go here. Settings.
Property
thingy.
Wait, that's on transcript. What
then? What about this?
Oh, I did not put this. What is wrong
with me? Wait one second.
F
metadata.
Meta dot
has chat dot. Wait, what?
Just has chat is enough. Wait a minute.
What the
meta?
I thought I fixed that
hashtag.
Oh, okay. Okay. Both works. Okay. Got
it. I understand now. Okay. Copy this.
Bind this as well.
All right. And Ba
uh that is enough I guess. Yeah,
I have to change the display of it,
right? Okay. preview.
Uh,
Twitch.
God, it's so laggy.
Twitch live chat replay. Okay, I'll have
to make this button smaller later.
Uh, okay. So, if I go to
this stream
XP
XB Oh, wait. It should show up here.
Wait. Oh, wait. I did not publish it.
Never mind. So, I have put this here and
go there.
Also, I have to fix the thumbnail rate
of the video player.
Damn. So, it takes a bit time to load
the thing. Okay. Okay. Two chat is here.
Two chat is here. Okay. Let me fix this
guy first.
Uh,
thumbail
dot.
Okay. Why are you being such a brat?
That thumbnail is working. Then why are
you
HQ default? Huh?
Is it because of the height 100
but 1280
720?
No. Huh? Weird.
Wait. Does YouTube not like,
huh? Weird.
Weird. That's so weird. That's so weird.
Okay. Anyone? Uh, Twitch. Twitch chat.
Everyone from Twitch,
we going to do you
h what? It's not linked.
it.
Wait, why is it saying zero? What the
heck?
What?
What
chapters are here?
Oh my god.
Wait, did it not link the Twitch chat?
What?
H these are my uh transcripts. Uh
YouTube transcripts. Wait, live chat.
YouTube. Thank you for That's YouTube
chat. Wait, why Twitch is empty? Boy,
what?
Okay, let me publish it at least. What
the heck was that?
Okay, that's weird.
I have to fix this.
Wait, there was an end point. I can
debug this. I I remember I made it
specifically
to debug. Oh,
what was it? Oh, okay. Okay, got it. uh
API slash archive slash
video ID
radio ID
uh slash
slash
chat What?
Uh,
no. This is YouTube.
Okay. Well, let me just put this whole
thing and debug this. What this? What is
going on?
What is going on? Um
uh
so it seems my Twitch chat
stuff is not
there when I do slash API
Oh,
Twitch object is empty.
Is there
missed? Can we also make the end point
end point be like slash API slash
archive slash video ID slash
chat slash you slash
YouTube
chat
slash chat
Twitch too
to
check This
uh
okay let me check this whole thing
empty is likely to worker cannot find
your Twitch va in streams.json Jason,
what your worker needs to exactly
extract the vault like this
if any of these missing workers does
okay
streams
confirm this ID access. Look at that.
Ah, APS streams is actually my Oh. Oh,
yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, this works, right? Yeah. Blob. Blob.
The fall the falls to your Oh,
it seems like it's not fetching it.
Weird.
What is wrong with those?
Twitch dot broadcast.
What the heck?
I see this then. Why is it not
Twitch broadcast. We have board ID.
Uh, okay. I think something's wrong.
Okay. Uh
handle full
handle
chat
right now your works but must mirror
handle Beautiful logic.
Twitch variety
chat pomiz. It is supposed to be
correct. It is correct though then I
don't get it why
uh
wait handle full what who is handle Oh.
Ah, this guy. Okay. Wait.
Video ID lang simplified and okay. Map
rest. Map rest.json. Okay.
What?
Okay. GitHub. Okay. Talk next
archive.
That is correct. Then what?
Oh my god, I hate debugging.
Yo, in handle chat. Okay, that is
correct.
Your full Twitch integration is also
correct. Okay, nice.
Why? Cuz does not contain the mapping.
I have to Okay, wait. I think I get an
idea. I got an idea.
this.
What?
What is a single end point?
Wait.
Archive
SL. Okay, got it. Archive.
AR. Okay. I don't read any streams.
Okay. Got it. Archive SL this
Twitch chat. Okay.
Has chapters. True. Has summary. True.
Available transcripts. I That's a
broken. It's fine.
Uh, we can fix the laterers
chat twitch.
Why is it bro
YouTube?
Why is there empty object?
And I do slash
and I did slash API slash video.
I did
I got this
Uh,
I I forgot my
u my my API reference thingy.
Where is it?
Uh,
API reference. Oh, I forgot you. Where
are you?
Oh, got it. stream dot
appear slash stream/
video ID.
Yeah, Twitch is there literally.
Why can't you see this?
Ed which length.
See the structure.
The code for extracting the v ID is
correct.
But brother, I can't get it.
Okay, replace the twist section with
this. Okay,
fine.
Uh, handle tad handle handle handle
handle.
Wait, I have a edge function. Oh, what?
What? How?
Page max age
30. What is that? Any
AI handler transcript chat? Okay.
Oh my god, this thing.
Can I get it working? Okay, deploy.
Um, this is how the
Looks like
fetching. What is parallel? Par
parallel.
Parallel. Oh my god, I can't pronounce
that word. What is happening?
Parallel.
Parallel. P. Parallel.
parallel.
Parallel.
Yeah, it seems the Twitch
when doing
My god, that's
kind of weird though. Oh,
I hope I respond.
instead of this corn stream that occurs
the array. Okay.
I'll let Twitch be null
and just
copy. Uh this put it here.
One slighter.
And now every Twitch request scans the
whole stream list. Better architecture.
Will the video stream app once? What?
Uh
fix collection loop. Uh stream data.
Stream app.
Let's stream data be null.
Ah, this wait I forgot about this guy.
Oh, never mind.
declared
declared what should I do even if it's
not declared
also
check the
So as sure
audrey mistake and that you wrote bought
this
use the is not needed anymore because
you switched to
dream list. Oh,
I didn't need it. Oh,
didn't even know that.
Okay,
what does here
available language
hydration?
I I am
deploy.
Hi
Oh, I actually read it correctly.
Oh,
no. Twitch. What is wrong with you?
corrected version. Okay, I did it. Why
rest of is actually correct?
>> Virtual ID. Okay, right now your full
endpoint JSON earlier in chat you used
data.
So I will change this to this. Okay,
wait.
Uh
okay fine
earlier. Okay. So change
what's wrong with the water. I
understand
messages Twitch data.
Okay. Format.
Hi. Uh
None. I know.
It's saying
why
there.
Did I actually find a
So your current
so look like object which means you Look
at your bed.
What? What?
Huh? Huh?
What the?
What?
and all streams.
Okay. Wait.
API slasharchive
slash streams
gives me this a list
array
containing ing all my channels videos
it's mainly
mainly from the YouTube repo
repo
slash
data slash
slash data slash uh
streams json
all the
uh yeah streams don't do
I off.
All right, guys.
So, real structure may be actually where
Oh, da.
Draw.
Ah,
so yeah. Uh,
the
I think the culprit was the
What?
There's not a list of stream. What do
you mean? Okay. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh.
Yeah. Yeah. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Cut it. Loop. Replace all
N.
Yeah.
What?
All right. This dummy dum dum
dreams are Jason.
aka
gives me this. What are you on about?
It's a list of video IDs, not the object
containing video ID data. What?
Oh my god. Chat GPT is glitching. It's
glitching. Oh my god.
Is it because my chat is long? Oh my
god.
Actually got Yeah, I'm correct. Of
course, I'm correct.
It's not an array. It's just structured
like what are you on about brother?
It is not structured
structured.
Oh my god.
So,
GitHub
data is a array.
Oh my god. I have to base this.
Oh my god.
Dum dum
pet [\h__\h] from stream map which is on TV
that has it. Just
check what I did with YouTube in the
YouTube.
Oh my god. You
and do that. No,
the worker should not read Twitch war
info from Jifa at all. It should read
from KV. Yes, finally.
Thank you.
Yes. Okay. Finally,
GP. Okay. Thank you. You dumb.
You stupid.
Why
did it take
20 minutes to make you understand?
Oh my god.
Twitch handler. Okay, finally Twitch
handler. Come on.
Okay, copy this whole thing. Paste.
And uh
you still have the broken order. Okay,
since we are using KV now uh we can
remove all that and
okay const effect. Okay, wait.
Uh
oh, got it. Uh remove all of this and
put this
H.
Oh, yeah. I I don't I have to use CL and
Gemini. Both of them are good now.
So,
sorry. Hi.
H I accidentally closed. H No.
Okay. Conser us. Okay. Where is it?
You should call streamer multiple times.
Creator helper.
What?
Con stream. What?
Huh?
what your Twitch handle should do.
Instead of this, you should do
a way to get video ID. Okay.
Uh
uh the Ker
What is an eye?
Oh,
remove this.
Hi
What the what
honey? Okay.
Ah.
Uh,
enter. Okay. Wait. Instead of stream map
a way to fetch a GitHub
JSON
you should do
uh correct all
source
that's more
then let Twitch v ID is equal to null.
have stream data at okay
in your handle full you still have the
broken order okay
this will crash since you're using KV
now you can remove the end block and
just do cons data is equal to a a
yeah I did that since you call multiple
creator helper
Okay.
Uh
helper
ah connect
and then I use
stream data await video ID.
Ah
no. Okay. Okay. Okay. I did it. Okay.
Okay, I'm going to deploy.
Ma,
everything is correct now. Okay, deploy.
Uh, please work.
I did my best. Let's see it in action.
Okay.
Uh,
hi. Enter.
Why?
YouTube. Okay, YouTube works.
Twitch.
Oh my god. Oh,
why?
This is not working.
Help. But
B and four times. What?
Oh, wait. Oh my god. Wait. What? Hello.
What the What the Hey.
What the? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I p I put it four times.
It
Oh my god.
How?
Oh, hon. I accidentally pasted it four
times. My keyboard. Oh,
okay. What?
No joke.
Bet you are.
Okay. Async handle chat.
Async and chat. Okay. As chat timeline
membership
handle for
Oh,
what kind?
What did I
No, but YouTube worked. It's only Twitch
who's acting like a brat.
The morning
What the
stream? Yes, stream map.
and their cars now.
Wait.
Oh my god, I'm so tired.
Mi
API archive full.
Oh,
hi.
All right.
I don't get it. Why is it hard?
Am I I think I made some mistake
somewhere.
Somewhere somewhere.
Oh boy.
Why am I getting error?
Oh, someone is calling mate. Uh, I'll be
back.
Oh god, I have to deal with
documentation.
by another yabby. I I have to fix
also. Yeah.
I mean all video ideas that uh we do
etc.
There's still the
Okay. In your Twitch chat, you currently
fetch.
Okay. Uh hello.
Okay. This is the guy who called
deleted.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I have to forward
this.
Hi. Anyway, uh in your Twitch chat,
fetch your cor. Okay. Coins. Oh,
if contains Okay, then you must do Okay.
There. I'll do that.
Const map. Const map. Const map. Const
map. Const const.
Oh yeah, my keyboard is doubling.
Control V there.
Deploy.
Uh-huh.
Okay. Pretty print.
Uh, back from the Okay, I'll just copy
this guy.
Okay.
Enter.
Whatever key is she
told me actually went like Yes.
Uh, current way replace this.
Oh my god.
Helper guide. Oh my god.
Ah, correct. Okay.
Oh, I have to do it like Okay, I'm so
dumb. Okay. Ah.
Oh my god, I'm so dumb. Okay, got it.
Got it. Got it.
Honey,
I got it right though. The more
Fix your helper function. Okay, wait.
Stream
map helper. Okay, get stream that. Wait.
Ah,
J
stream map.
Uh check the code.
Okay. One second.
Okay,
you're doing conate. Okay,
replace the section.
Don't go.
Got a Twitch block.
Okay, I did it. Okay, you already
created a helper but in you did not use
it
cleaner version.
Handle chat.
Amazing.
And those do.
Ah, okay.
Okay, I'm deploying it.
Got him.
Oh, blah blah blah blah blah. Uh,
I'm still getting error.
Can we do debug on
chat slash Twitch?
My brain is hurting from all of this.
Honestly,
deploy.
Oh my god. Why?
Okay. M.
Uhhuh. Uh,
this is so weird. This is so weird.
H, been looking. Uh, but I have to head
to bed now. Oh, hello.
Hello. It's been a while. Hello. Hello.
How was your stream?
I was struggling with some dev stuff.
Hi, have a good uh
have a good night ahead and sleep well.
Yes, I have steady stuff too. I'm like
balancing both.
Hi.
Sleep well.
Twitch chat. Uh-huh.
Why GPD? Why you break?
Also, I have to set up also I have to do
this documentation stuff. You know what?
I'm going to mute my mic. I'm just going
to hold it. I need my passport and stuff
I need to send to this guy. Oh god. Oh
god. BRB. Okay.
And I'll fix this cloudfare thing.
Oh my god, I have to And this uh
I got it. Who actually got it?
I look so bad. I did update my pictures.
I'm back.
Anyway, what am I saying about this?
Okay, I do not have this thing. I have
to download this from this code.
Okay, you don't see anything, right?
Okay, nice. Uh,
okay.
I have to get this code and put it here.
Okay. And
And this
will do that.
Why am I Why am I humming? Black pender.
No. No. Is it black? No. Pink panther.
So pink panther dash.
there.
Where is it?
One thing.
Okay. Uh,
that's sorted.
Back to Cloudfare.
Um, how does YouTube stuff
use the correct video ID, etc. Here
I don't get it.
Why Twitch stuff needs the
stream map. Um
um my ending.
Wait, do I not have the back side of
this one?
I don't have it.
Oh, I do not have it.
Ah, one second.
Okay. Twitch file chat files are stored
by V ID and not YouTube ID. For example,
Twitch. Okay. API request is okay. Only
knows this. Not okay. I understand.
Oh god.
H. So I need to bind the stream map
here. Okay fine. binding
KV name space add binding
streams
the word KV
one And
oh my god. Uh uh. Duplicate.
Duplicate
this.
What did I do for my other stuff, man?
Stream engine. What did I do? Streams
KV. Okay. Streams under
KV.
Add binding.
which is fastest small memory scalable
to thousands of streams.
Okay. So I binded
binded the KV it's variable
S.
Replace everything that says
okay. Change this to this.
Okay.
Uh
uh. Okay. Got it. Um
edit
the over complications be pain.
stream app. Okay. Env Okay. Capital
streams underscore KV.
Also, my my keyboard is duplicating
keys. Why?
Oh my god. duplicating
like I replaced it in three places.
One, two, three.
Deploy.
And we check it again.
Refresh.
Ah, I got it. Yes. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Add a break is starting now.
What the silly bot silly bot
bot badge version one
ad brick.
That's it.
Huh?
That is it. Jocknix is live now
streaming. Just chatting gorilla back
from the void. Okay. Okay. But that's
it. Wait. What the Where is the whole
body?
One second. My message.
Uh, okay. Okay. We We got it. We got it.
Wait, wait. Um,
C, see. Finally. Okay. Archive SL video
ID/ chat/ Twitch. I get this much. I see
fossa bot. I see Siri bot
for sur.
But where is the whole chat though? But
I I don't get it. But yeah.
Okay. Chat dot twitch dot.
So I go to archive.
Refresh.
Oh, wait. Alexa archive.
We got it. We got it.
Oh,
we got it. Christian, let's go.
inside this.
Okay, first one is time stamp.
Hi.
One second. I'm getting calls. One
second.
Okay, my bad. Uh, my dad was calling me.
Uh, hi time stamp. But got it.
Uh, hi. Oh, wait. I have to convert the
time. No.
Uh. Oh, wait. I can add
add uh
add uh time time localization time.
Uh,
come on.
Copy that.
It
Oh my god, my keyboard. Okay.
Hi. Time stamp.
height fourth too much. Now we don't
need this.
Now image avatar user image right
message use uh user dot
user dot
m wait
a URL is not here. What
message dot e
what
badge?
What
badge color color name? What? What?
What?
M.
Oh my god.
I forgot you avatar URL.
Oh my. I forgot.
No.
Oh, it's not here. Oh my god. Oh. Oh,
there. I'll fix it. Uh,
scripts.
Normalize chat.
Normalize chat. Okay. Normalize V ID.
Rogate ID. Okay. Uh game. Oh, no, no,
no. Messages. Uh flag.
You know what? Copy the whole thing.
GPT.
Uh GitHub.
Uh
Twitch.
I have to delete the file.
Oh, channel. Okay.
Oh my god, my mouse. No, my mouse is
lagging.
N. My mouse is lagging. Okay. O.
Oh my god. Stop playing.
Oh, wait.
Okay, it's back.
So for um
so for uh
normalized chats uh chat
JSON there is no user avatar URL. So, I
need that and the nor Hello Dia,
welcome. It's been a while. How are you
doing?
Let me just switch.
Uh, for no reason. I need that in the
normaliz
help.
Welcome. How you doing?
Uh
includes the ads avatar URL
uh human readable time.
Okay,
I'm doing great. What about you? I'm
also doing okay.
just doing some work and also
steady stuff. Mhm.
Uh
what else do we need? Only this thing,
right?
Paste this. Come.
I'll
actions
scripts
that uh this
normalize. I will delete this file and
we are good.
Delete file comment
actions. Okay,
let's see it in action then.
Twitch archive
random flow.
Hi. Let's go. This should do it.
Probably it has to do it. Let's hope it
does it.
I run it.
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Line 96.
Ext
96 96 this guy.
Wait, did I double copy? Oh my god.
Wait, I double copy. Oh
my
My p my keyboard is broken.
Single copy doesn't. Okay. Come.
I was like this is the third fourth time
my double copy.
Yes, it created a file. Yay.
code
that uh
net
normalized.
So yeah, avati hi hi hi
refresh.
hot.
And uh
inside this
uh dot
user dot avatar URL
look
Oh my god. Oh,
tw
you. Oh my god. Nice, nice, nice, nice,
nice, nice, nice.
Oh, what is this?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Username
uh
user dot.
Should I show display name or login
name?
Display name.
Hi
message
dot.0
dot.
Text dot
Oh, that is an emote, right?
Uh what?
Why? I don't know. Why is there so many
emotes?
Ah, emote name, emote type. Okay.
H.
How do I get my emote?
Huh?
H.
Yeah. Emote. Yeah. emot.
What the
uh
display
and display name
message.
Uh
oh. 0 0. Oh yeah. Yeah. I have to do
this now. Readable time stamp. But ah
uh
Yeah.
Okay. Um
timestamp is
collection item dot. Oh, I have it.
Okay. Okay. Okay. This one. Okay. Okay.
It's HMS. Okay. Okay. Okay. I do not
need time stamp then.
Go
a break
human readable.
Hi. Okay. Nice, nice, nice. time stamp.
So the idea is when So the idea is this.
Okay. In uh in the upcoming updates
I you click on here click there video
player there.
Uh so yeah if you click on this it'll go
up to here
like that. I have to do that. Hi,
YouTube.
This is so good.
Where is she?
Oh my god.
Now I have to merge both. I have to
multi multi I have to make it a multi-
chat. That's the next idea.
merging YouTube, Twitch, kick chat into
one.
So,
huh.
Okay, we need to do something about the
emote. Emote.
Okay, I'll switch.
Okay, one second. I have to attend some
calls. Not BRB. No.
Hi. Yeah, bye. Okay, I'm back. Sorry, I
had to
I I replied to the call. My sensei
called me.
Today is the last date for the payment
for the
payment got to last date.
So yeah, I'm like uh my as I'm also
doing that while I'm doing this
uh taking calls and balancing.
Okay. Uh Twitch chat. No emote. Okay.
Emote. What can I do with you? H
Okay, I have an idea.
So, uh,
wait, I think I need a good, uh,
ah, this guy is a good example. Okay,
wait.
What? It's a text. Huh?
Add break is starting.
Type text type emote. Okay.
Wait, how do you
Okay. Uh,
so cool.
archive. Okay.
Uh, so it works. Thank you.
So I had a doubt.
How can I make Twitch emotes
show up in my archive page? So, for the
collection
component,
I
uh since the message object for
normalize chat chat.json T is like this.
Uh
is like this.
Help me do the
JS expression and web studio.
App Studio
App Studios Express
Editor.
So the thing is sometimes it's text and
some
and sometimes it's remote. If a user
message is
uh message contains both text and emote.
I want
both to be shown inside
and I can show this now.
Uh
as of right now
just
uh all uh as of right now only message
text is shown
I want to include
both and is it possible to
get the whole
emote image in here
somehow?
Or do I need a
use like uh
image
component
and
do show hide
show hide dome
logic for it. Please help. Okay,
a part of me is thinking I have to do
some logic
render text inside. You don't need to
separate DOM output HTML if you join
parts. Okay, looks like this H
expression
collection item part amazes Odyssey
join.
Oh, okay. Okay, okay. Twitch URL is
Twitch V2 emotes static CDN.jtvn.net
net emoticons V2 immort ID. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Ah okay. Um
no. Okay. Okay. Okay. Uh so
wait for board has the
emote, right?
Ah, you don't have a
anyone. Uh,
it is wrong.
Map is not a function.
I get this.
Oh, pain
wow
wow wow wow.
Add a collection. What? Inside chat
message. Oh.
Oh, you wanted me to do that. Okay. Oh,
smart.
So, apparently I
delete this binding
inside message. I add a com uh
collection
map studio could load my PC
now.
Okay. Put this inside
here.
Wait.
So this collection
will be collection item dot
message.
Yes.
Remove the span.
Hi
go there.
We have type ID, name, emote, text,
emote. Okay, we got two types, right?
Type text, type
emote, type text. Okay. 22
uh whatever
text is.
Oh, space. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Ah, space counts. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Uh, text pen and image pen.
Morning
text
and uh
image
mash.
Oh,
hi.
So,
this guy would be a collection item.
Dot.
Uh
number five, huh?
You're not Oh god. Uh
show only when type is equal to text.
Okay, I made the
nested collection
and made a text pan and
image component.
Give me the expression stuff.
Uh,
you only need three small imp uh
expressions. All right.
Type physical to text
dot text, right?
collection item dot.
Wow.
Oh, wait. I can just Oh, yeah. Yeah.
What the
[\h__\h] What the [\h__\h]
Could I uh inside?
Ah,
okay. Collection item dot
text.
Hi.
Okay.
Text
now. Uh
this thing proofs
uh
show condition.
If I am correct, I have to do
question mark space
false
and put that.
Is that correct?
Oh, that is correct. Yay.
Now this guy image
election ID
Ah, double
collection
dot.
Uh whatever
collection item
uh past it here.
I need
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Look.
Let's go.
Yay.
Nice.
Y
emote.
Hey, okay, I fixed it.
Switch the
style that
block is an eye flex.
Flex.
Uh, busy.
Wait, why does it look odd?
M m.
Okashi
okashi.
Okashi.
Ah, okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. I
understand. Okay.
Alexa.
Ah, it's pan. Okay. Uh, DIV div
keyboard. I got
uh and this would be
flex.
Yes.
Oh no, the immortal getting strung.
Ah!
Oh no, no, no, no, no. I have to fix
you. I have to fix you.
Don't lag.
Stop lagging.
Uh why is it like this?
O uh wait
px vertical line margin 02.
Oh. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. I can do
that. Okay. I can do that. Okay. I can
do that. Yeah. Uh
image
old
collection item
dot
name
Hick
thingy.
I can h make it so that when people
hover over the emote, it shows the emote
name,
right?
But then one would say, okay, then what
about normally?
Yeah, I shouldn't not do that. Um
uh
so um
28 vertical line middle
height
28 px X.
Why is it broken? Okay.
Uh
vertical.
Yeah. Vertical line. N middle
and my DDL.
Okay, then what?
Margin 02.
What does that mean?
Margin
uh more.
I add this
margin
cocoa.
Stop. Right, left, right. Uh
I can't
zero.
What does the margin do to I can just
ask GT
meaning
top bottom zero left right two okay
what the I don't need to do this like
manually
oh my god it's so laggy Okay.
Ocean coin close.
Okay,
it do be laggy.
And you see it's animated too. No,
that that makes me happy, man.
Also, this is weird.
It's not aligned correctly.
That should look like this. 90 seconds.
Add this emote here. than this, right?
It looks like a weird
and to
Yeah, keep spacing
and zero. Okay, that is zero.
Didn't need to change anything. So yeah,
I'm Z.
But this guy
What is the best way?
I think I need to add more spacing. Baby
start.
Ah, Zender. Zender. Sender. Zender. The
E.
So we could
I don't know what to do.
It's supposed to look like a paragraph,
but this looks so bad.
I'll take a screenshot like that and ask
here in this example
looks weird. It has two text and one
emote. I
what
an actual example of
looks from Twitch chat.
How can I How can I make it work to the
Oh, wait. I forgot to Oh.
Come on.
I accidentally pressed um
Display in nine whites space pre
what
display in line.
Select your message. Can I change to
block?
Oh, text pan is supposed to be inline.
That is a thing.
Oh my god, it's so laggy.
Stop lagging.
Pizzy
block.
Oh, both of them has to be inline block.
Okay. What is an inline block?
Pre wrap white space pre wrap.
Okay.
I'll bet in line.
Oh, it's 12.
Okay. White space. White space.
White space.
White.
Add a custom CSS property.
How about
Yeah, it's 4 hours. I'll just wrap up
after this.
So givea
I will take a rest and I'll later I'll
do it.
Uh,
white
white space.
Um,
it's called preap.
Quiet. Should
I just look for three?
No.
What? Okay. White
white.
Oh my god. PC
white
space.
Breathe
up.
Ra bread
and line middle.
I don't see the white uh white space
thingy. I'm so confused.
in line.
Nothing happens. I just want it to be
one line.
I know.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I changed the whole object to an inline
yata. Okay, I fixed it. Oh my god, I
fixed it. Okay, this is what I just had
to do. I just had to put everything in.
Okay.
Oh my god. Done.
Twist chat is done.
Nice, nice, nice.
Oh my god.
So get Oh my god, I'm yawning.
Hi publish.
Don't worry much.
Oh, I must
message.
Oh, wait. Uh, immortal, right?
text
txt.
Okay.
Oh, stop.
And that's how everyone I finally merged
a Twitch chat to a YouTube stream
theme. The whole database is on powered
by YouTube. Uh like based on YouTube
video ID. I finally linked Twitch chat
to a video. YouTube video. Oh my god,
that's a big thing.
Nexus kick.
Oh my god. Nexus kick.
Yeah. Then I had to do multiream of
this.
I put indep individual chats. Right.
Next is the multiream version.
So, so,
oh yeah, I added one more thing. Uh, m
uh
added one more thing. Where is it?
I do one more thing.
Okay. hasht dot
a
o
meta dot.
Oh my god. Oh no. Where is YouTube? Oh,
that this is bad.
True false deny you. Oh no. Where is
butter?
I need to change this uh quickly.
Okay, let's let me just switch my
screen.
Uh,
all right. I'm not reading the chat. I'm
sorry. Hello, Zen. Uh, Zen Game Z Gamer.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Oh my god. You sent
message two minutes ago. I didn't read
it. Sorry. Sorry. Hello. Welcome to the
stream.
Hello. Hello.
I'm I was just doing my archive system
stuff.
Hello
then the gamer. Welcome to the stream
for meta stuff. I wanted uh
so basically what I'll do is I'll do
conditional rendering
uh if
the
you uh stream has
what do you call it like there are past
broadcast right which doesn't have
Twitch linked Twitch broadcast ID linked
right so in those case scenarios I just
want the YouTube chat to be shown right
for the user who checks the archive page
and
uh the issue with meta
a meta object which has has chat is
equal to true false thingy the thing is
people who view the past broadcast I'll
show you what I'm trying to say
okay for example
uh archives page right
so uh we know that this stream is linked
to Twitch right so let's take uh this
stream which does not have Twitch linked
like the art creator stream right so our
creator stream is there
why is it not loading
What?
Hey, what?
Um, I need a h Yeah, it loaded. Okay,
load it. Needed just a refresh. Okay, so
yeah, you see the issue. Twitch is not
linked, but Twitch chat is showing, but
it's empty. You don't want that. Yeah,
you did like chat that this is correct,
but
I don't want Twitch to show yet. So I
need to specify and separate the
conditional thingy.
Yeah.
Hello Syria. Welcome.
Welcome D. How you doing? Long time.
Yes. It's been so long. How are you?
Hello.
Uh
separate YouTube chat and Twitch chat.
You uh you seem tired. Yeah, I slept
only 3 hours. So, so today I had like
class uh at 6:00 uh and I woke up at
3:00 a.m. I slept at 11 or 12 or
something. Uh
yeah, this is the reason why I don't
want to stream. Actually, I feel so dead
inside and tired tired all the time.
Okay. Yeah, I know.
Yeah. I'm going to go sleep after this.
Oh, I Okay, show this.
I'm going to go sleep after this. It's
almost done, though. It's almost done.
Uh, you know, I made like an archive
page.
I made an archive page. Now you can see
your chats for the specific stream. It's
like a public archive.
Uh
okay, let me show you. Um so I have a
archive page joking. Space live stream
uh hyphen
uh archives. So like say yesterday's
stream I did.
You click on my stream.
Don't mind the thumbnail. It's broken.
Uh I'll fix it because it's uh that
stream thumbnail was an HD quality so
480p.
So that's bad. Anyway, you can watch the
stream
uh uh from here and there'll be Billy
Billy as well. Then you can see the
description of the YouTube stream. You
can see the transcripts, the whole
transcripts you see from YouTube
that thing. And you can see your live
chat, YouTube chat,
and your Twitch chat. I just added
today. You have your Twitch chat. I have
to link kick. And there's AI based uh uh
chapters. I I'm going to make it so that
you click on the timestamp here and it
will jump to the video. I'll do that
later. And AI summary as well.
And also uh this does this this thing
did not get populated. Uh apparently
you're supposed to get populated here if
I can show this. Oh my god. I can't
uh yeah so there's like um
one second.
Oh my god. Notion come on. So there's
supposed to be this thing. Um yeah I'll
take the Valerant stream as an example.
There's manual data as well. For
example, if someone donated to me or
anything, I have to automate that later
in the future. But for now, I'm making
it manual. So, I have like I'll change
the name to like jock stuff, jock
creator notes or something. Then, if I
have any stream goals or something goals
post uh for a specific stream, I can put
it here. I can put it in notion. Wait,
I can put it in notion and it'll show up
and if I have any reviews how the stream
was. Oh yeah, this one. This one. So I
can manually write content here. Uh I'll
remove timestamps uh cuz I have it AI
based now. Yeah. And here I'll add the
thing where uh contributions or
something um community contributions or
support. So if someone subscribed um
like on Twitch or donated bits, cheers,
uh membership, anything, I can put their
names here and it will show up in the uh
stream uh like website, right?
So yeah, it's like an archives thingy.
Every data, everything will be here.
Yeah.
I have to like work on the Billy Billy
one as well. I have it here. Uh if I can
find it,
uh tabs list.
Yeah, Billy Willy is here. But um I have
to somehow
send data here to my database.
So I stopped using uh Sammy to uh make
my database stuff
streams buffering. Ah
of my my PC my PC dying. O
yeah if my stream is buffering it's my
PC dying.
Why?
So, yeah. Uh I don't know if you can
still hear me, but uh I was saying um I
moved everything to
uh Cloudfare. I moved everything to
Cloudfare. I have like uh workers now,
notion stuff, uh Discord stuff is
automated. Even this is automated by
Clifair. Uh I I have like uh
I have like a GitHub for Twitch and for
YouTube.
Uh wait wait wait
for Twitch and YouTube. Uh this will
have my thumbnails, my live chat, AI
based uh summary and uh AI based summary
and chapter markers. And I have the
timeline thingy as well. timeline is
basically um it looks like this. Uh how
can I?
So it's basically like my uh transcript
the YouTube SRT thingy, right? Like the
subtitle with the chat if there's a
chat. Yeah, both shows up in one thingy.
That's not needed. But yeah, for
subtitle I put like um Japanese,
Chinese, simplified and traditional and
English and English origin. So four
languages
if you count two uh additional
Englishes.
So yeah,
and I can use this for like I can dump
this file into video editor if I want.
It's all saved here. Yep. And my live
chat stuff is here.
What else? And yeah, of course, the
thumbnail thing.
Thumbnail. [\h__\h]
Thumbnail is always stored up here.
Yeah. And this is the one. Uh, it checks
from GitHub for the Discord events.
For the Discord events, it checks from
GitHub. This one I need to fix it. This
is today's stream. I don't know why it
did not get sent.
Uh
oh my god.
So yeah, I uh the stuff I did all these
uh all these months on Sammy,
I did it in 5 days. It took me three
months to finish all of this. Improve
and improve, make it better, the whole
database stuff. And now it took me five
days to just implement everything on the
cloud. So I don't need to run my PC,
right? I can just simply go live on my
phone. No PC needed and everything will
be automated.
So go the show.
I'm feeling proud though.
Ah, I worked hard.
Even though I'm not supposed to do this
any of this, but I did it.
Huh. But yeah, next idea is a schedule
page. Uh main thing for making this
whole thing is actually for schedule.
So whenever there's an upcoming stream,
uh basically a remake of this guy,
this schedule thingy, right? Yeah. Yeah,
this guy will be remade on my website
properly
with proper visualization and
everything. Um, yeah, upcoming streams
will be there. Currently live stream
will be there. Completed streams will be
there. No, wait. I think I'll I'll put
like a link for the archive page.
Yeah,
since No, like I'm not like a big
YouTuber, right? to get myself on like
um
to get myself on like um holo decks and
stuff, right? So like for example, face
connect, they use the holo deck stuff if
I'm correct. Oh, wait, they changed Oh,
never mind. They changed it. Okay, never
mind. Oh, they changed it. What?
Oh, they changed it. What?
They changed it. Which API do they use?
Right. What they changed it?
Wow.
But wait, which which agency uses holo
text
schedules?
Uh
uh.
But yeah, the uh holex is only for big
YouTubers. No, you need a certain amount
of subs and numbers, right? I can't get
myself on on there sadly. So, I have to
make my own localizer system.
Yeah,
but it works.
But yeah, they did something like this.
Wow, that is so cool. Wait,
okay, I'll take inspiration from this.
He So, they show V. Oh,
okay. Okay. This is a time stamp. Oh,
god.
Probably channel banner. YouTube channel
banner. Okay.
Huh. What did they use? This is nice. I
could also do it like Yeah. Upcoming
streams, right? I schedule on YouTube.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Are these all
scheduled on YouTube? Oh, they are.
Okay. Okay. Okay. They're using YouTube
API. Okay.
I got you. Okay. Live streams will be
like this. Okay.
Yeah. Wow. Nice. So, everything is
YouTube. Okay. They are using YouTube
API. Wow.
So if the v if the video privacy status
is
uh public no u if the life cycle status
is like what um or the va broadcast
content type is complete then it shows
the vaude. That is smart. Oh my god.
Okay that is smart. Wait this is a
Twitch stream though. How are they
putting Twitch over here?
Wait.
Okay. They Wait. What do they do?
Hey,
they both are same.
What?
Hey.
So, they also put you put the YouTube uh
know Twitch V link too. Okay. I'm
getting inspiration from that.
That is so cool.
I don't know if these people uh face
kind of talents like multiream or
something. I think she does. Yeah, too.
But crazy. They have Twitch man that is
nice and cool. See Twitch videos here.
How? Okay. YouTube TW. Okay. Okay. So
they are linking it
similar to what I'm doing maybe but they
have they have to track multiple
channels now h probably using holodex
API holodex already has everything
uh normalized now and easier to access
any
what were we you what were we doing
again um I needed Uh, conditional
rendering.
Yeah, they got a theme. Yep. Yep.
Must be nice.
And it's crazy that I did all of this
myself by power of AI cuz I don't know
how to code.
Oh god, I may fix this.
Okay. Return. Where is the return?
Ask chat. Right. We change it to like
this.
Wait a minute. Why does it look weird?
Um
I also read my I made everything hand. I
mean m is 3D one. I hold it every now
and still think. Oh nice. Good luck.
Good luck though. Good luck. Good luck.
You got this.
Okay, I will deploy this.
Go back to this guy. So, we going to do
conditional rendering over here.
Twist. Okay, refresh the API.
Man, I don't know when I will debut my
model stuff. Uh, probably I think when
I'm in Japan. Oh, probably on my
birthday.
How do you even figure out what to put
where?
Which one?
N.
What to put where?
Okay. YouTube.
YouTube is done and Twitch is here.
Now, what's left for me is kick quotes
and stuff. Oh, GPD tells me where to
put.
Yeah, GPD tells me, you know.
So, I just do that. Like here it said
um this is my current, right?
This is my current uh I have to search
for this line
here like Ctrl F search for it. So, I
got the this thing and I change it.
Change it to this. Then I update my
return. That's it.
Yeah. Let's do the powerful improvement
stuff.
Ragd Doll. Yeah, that is true as well.
Yeah.
Oh,
the only thing which one I feel like I
need to improve is the
um only thing I think I need to improve
now is
yeah this uh this CSS of this these
stuff now this looks odd weird I love to
I love to fix it. Al I'm not even
supposed to have videos which were like
so older like November 18. I was only
supposed to keep 2026 videos from here
onwards. Yeah, our collab.
Yeah, from here on was only I'm supposed
to keep it but I accidentally put like
30 and it logged all these dreams sadly.
But it's fine.
So now conditional rendering will
happen. This stream has Twitch and
YouTube. So Twitch and YouTube chat will
show up. Okay, good. That's working.
So for example, yes, they for
yesterday's stream.
Uh
yeah. Oh, wait. Why is it Twitch chat
showing here? O.
Oh, this is bad. It's not supposed to
show.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I Yeah. So, my
idea, next idea I want to do tomorrow or
today maybe, I don't know, is see this
is a example. The collab stream we did,
right? Okay, this is a good example.
I'll lose this. So, the collab stream we
did, right? If a user comes to my
archive page
like sees a collab stream, I want to
have like a section
over here
before the broadcast details giving each
specific collaborators details as in my
idea right was um my idea was um I have
this database system Wait,
I have this database system, okay?
Collab partners thingy.
This is like a old database I made,
okay? On notion, okay, it has everyone I
ever collabed with.
And I can just uh copy people's links
from here. I will like right click,
copy, right? And uh only one image
currently but I will expand it. I made
everything
uh yeah now I can put page content in
notion right and fetch it. So I can put
everyone's like collab partners old
avatars or new avatar or something. I
can keep it here if I want. But yeah
this is just for meish. No one can
access this page unless they have the
uh URL I think. But yeah, so my idea was
since
I uh since I put my data thingy on
uh CloudFare, right? Like all of my
stream stuff, right?
Like all of my uh stream stuff is here,
stream map. So that means like all
I think I am uh putting up to 41 streams
currently. So it looks like this.
All 41 streams looks like this. Right.
So I thought I'll make like a database.
This is the four collab partners. So uh
one entry now it will have like name of
the collab partner the username
universal uh display name
right cuz uh some people some uh
collaborators they have their YouTube
username different and Twitch username
different right so my plan was I'll have
a name object with their name then
inside it they'll have their YouTube
channel link their YouTube username
name, Twitch channel link, Twitch
channel uh username,
uh kick kick username, kick channel
link. Okay. And uh
yeah, and like nationality if uh yeah,
since I'm a international YouTuber, so
I'll put nationality. Then what else? Um
yeah so basically uh like there'll be a
section and I can just um I can just uh
link it now I can somehow link the
stream like
uh like slash collab
okay slash at for example surya sudia vt
then comma at miko
at uh I there I just have to do that
right and it will automatically
locate the locate your YouTube data like
YouTube URL, Twitch URL, cake URL, all
those stuff, Instagram, social media and
it will all uh populate here. So like it
will be a card where your like I'll make
it rounded
collaborator kind of thingy rounded with
the channel your YouTube channel icon or
like I can put like oh yeah I have to
put your avatar thingy right so I can
make it like your YouTube avatar or
something or I can just use from the
collab database right I have right like
that.
Oh my god, that's a great idea. Oh my
god.
So yeah, like
that. That's my idea. So like either
ways, like either ways like if you were
to for example um
like if anyone were to um Oh my god,
where is this? Yeah. So if anyone were
to like
um
like I don't need a right summary
anymore, right? Like cuz uh I can just
put my link here. It will already have
the metadata,
right? Like yeah uh metadata will be
here and the YouTube thumbnail will be
here. Like if I put this on Twitter and
stuff, it'll uh look like a YouTube
stream. No, you can't play the video,
but still like um yeah, metadata will be
there. No, which itself is nice.
Um I don't look like this if I'm
correct.
Uh if I just post that
yeah it'll look like this gorilla train
jocknik's archive right yeah it will be
easier now
so
I can delete this
so I don't need to write stuff so people
if they want to check the archive they
can see the data behind it.
So, yeah, quick setup and all the other
stuff always nice. Yeah, true, true,
true.
Oh my god.
This was an inspiration. This uh revamp
version two was an inspiration from my
old
website
uh dog.space.
I had this summary page long back last
year. Last last year 2024.
It looked like this
live stream summary. It looked like
this.
If you compare this and uh this is way
more improved, you know,
I think. Yeah, it's way more improved. A
lot of new stuff.
Uh live chat, YouTube chat. I I need to
fix this. um YouTube chat everything
etc.
Uh and here now it was so hectic like
look at this. This is how I used to I
have to normally type no manually type
like I have to type it in English. I
have to translate it and put it in
Chinese. I have to translate Chinese to
Japanese. It is hectic though like back
in I have to like uh manually do this. I
had to write it like this here.
and uh OBS recording uh timestamps. I
have to manually do this here.
I think I use Sammy to do this but still
it was like hectic.
So yeah and I have to upload the
thumbnail
manually on notion. Too much work.
Yeah. Now I don't need to do that. It u
like same system is there. Notion is
only for manual entry. So all the
streams will be automatically created
here with a slug like YouTube ID and the
title and it always uses the template.
So if I cl create a new page,
it'll automatically use the template,
right? I don't need a type. I if I need
a type, I just type here something.
That's it. Easy, right?
No need to press too many stuff.
It's so
really nice honestly.
Huh.
And only thing I need to fix with a
chapter marker is I have to put the
beginning 0 0. No, just like YouTube
timestamps. If you're putting timestamps
on YouTube, you have to put 00 first.
Then only rest of the time stamps work
here. It sucks starts from six. Now I
have to fix that.
I think you should put all these stream
where you're setting up BG after stream.
I was making a jog playlist. Yeah.
Wait. Background of the stream.
What do you mean?
Oh yeah, my V channel 24x7 channel,
right? I also revamped that. So this is
my W channel, right? I mean basically um
uh basically this is what it gets uh
streamed
like I only have one single I only have
one single browser. So the same link
right
uh which is currently live on YouTube
Twitch kick so I made a OBS scene system
so control like F12 right so I can do
currently it's on full screen mode right
if I'm live on TW currently I'm live on
my main channel
um so I have a thing
uh call live mode. So it makes the
player smaller.
It makes the player smaller and it h it
shows the schedule of all the next tree
all the next playlist. So if in if in
the playlist if first five videos are
done then sixth video is Hongai star
rail right. So it will switch to the
hungai star rail as highlighted. This is
broken for some reason. I have to fix
it. So yeah. So this was an inspiration
from Aspen Gold. So like Aspen Gold uh
24x7 channel. When Aspen Gold is live,
it shows like fan arts and stuff.
Currently, this is a rerun mode. This is
full screen when he's not live. But when
he is live, the video player gets
smaller. There's background music. Uh
there's the schedule. There's like the
playback of the ward is paused.
Oh my god, my PC
playback of the V is paused. Uh post and
there's fan arts
uh all the fan arts of Asangol that's
get that gets replayed like like what do
you call it like a slideshow kind of
thingy.
Yeah, I want to do that. I want to
somehow make a database for fan arts.
All the fan arts I ever received in my
whole existence, I just have to I want
to put it somewhere.
So yeah,
show the
but too much nerding stuff.
Uh,
by us.
Wow.
Okay. [\h__\h] Okay.
Entire history. Okay. Four or five.
Oh, I can make the chat. Oh,
timestamp based chat tip here like
Twitch war replay. Oh,
always trying to get better. Yeah.
Oh,
yeah. Idea can change your life.
Yeah, Ida can change your life.
Oh boy.
It was just a random idea
like one day ago.
Crazy.
But I'm really glad that I was able to
do this.
Honestly glad the
oy
what happened here.
11:40.
My Twitch archive is not working. What
the heck?
a galaxy GitHub
run the code.
Oh, it's working. Chat already exists.
So, yeah, when uh the g uh how it um how
it works now uh for the GitHub, how it l
So, this downloads the Twitch V. No, it
does not download the VOD but just the
chat
and then logs it. It fetches using
YouTube DLP. It fetches the Twitch V
then gets the video ID of the VOD and
uses the V ID to ask Twitch downloader
to like download the chat just the chat.
Yeah. So, I made this video and showed
my parents and they like remove super
for this.
Wow. Oh, no. I'm a Wait, what? Wait, did
Wait, you did face channel stuff when
Oh, you mean other channels?
Oh, boy.
Uh
video
n
I am one in the ocean of Okay, gotcha.
Hi.
Uh,
you too.
Where is where I make what I make
instead of wearing up?
Ah, gotcha.
Get
Windows installation. Okay.
have got three star. Oh my god. Crazy.
What?
That's crazy.
Honestly speaking, I I wanted to make um
tutorial on everything I'm doing and how
I did it, all of these stuff. No, but
then it hit then it then it hit me like
if I had to explain everything, it's
going to be a 3 4hour video and who's
going to watch it? People don't like
over complicated stuff, overexplained
stuff, right? So I'm like, yeah, I'll
not do a video or tutorial.
I'm like, let it be.
So yeah.
Oh boy, I'm so sleepy.
Okay. So, what else is left?
God, there's so much stuff, right? Yeah,
I have to make the V system.
I'm going to get back to work. Yeah,
rest up. I'll also wrap up. It's 5
hours.
We did so much today. I'll go sleep.
Maybe I'll stream in the night. Maybe. I
don't know.
But yeah, thank you for today everyone.
You eat well. Take care. Thank you for
dropping by.
It means a lot.
Oh my god.
Let me do this.
Yeah, it will automatically
make things. So, it's fine. I can just
end it.
Anyway, people people,
I'm going to be wrapping it up over
here.
Once again, thank you to those who came
by today. I know it's super boring. I
was just talking yapping while doing
some weird stuff.
But yeah, um no more gaming streams
since it's a busy month for me. Yeah.
Thank you for hanging out with me and
talking with me.
Thank you. Thank you all. And hope you
like the archive page I'm been making.
Uh but yes, thank you for today and have
a good one everyone. I'll go wrap up and
sleep and rest up. Got to study. I got
to revise for tomorrow. High
priorities.
So yeah, thank you all for coming by
today. What's the jo and have a good
one. Take care and have a nice one
everyone.
Hi